meetasianbabes.com 2015-12-06

# Terms of Use

**YOU MUST BE AT LEAST 18 YEARS OLD TO REGISTER ON THIS SITE.**

To become a Member you must register with us. When and if you register to become a Member, you agree to provide accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted by our registration form ("Profile") and to maintain and update your information to keep it accurate, current and complete. You agree that we may rely on your Profile as accurate, current and complete. You acknowledge that if your Profile is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete in any respect, we reserve the right to terminate this Agreement and your use of the Service.

The Owner or You may terminate this agreement at any time, for any reason whatsoever, effective upon sending written notice to the other party. If you send a notice of termination, your membership shall concurrently terminate, without an obligation to make a payment, rebate or refund on the part of the Owner. The Owner does however reserve the right to suspend or terminate your membership at any time, without notice, if you breach this Agreement or any other terms and conditions posted on the Site from time to time.

The Owner assumes no responsibility whatsoever for your use of the Service. It is for your sole, personal use and you may not distribute your user name and password allowing others to use the service through your membership. Use of the service is strictly prohibited to minors or any person under the age of 18, regardless of whether you have parental consent.

**As a member, you agree that:**

You will only use the Service in a manner that is accepted and legal according to all applicable laws and regulations.

You will adhere to our email and acceptable use policies and all other terms and conditions relating to your usage of the Services in respect of the Site, and will not transmit chain letters, junk messages, advertisements or any type of solicitation whatsoever of any products or services to any other Members of the Service.

You will not in any way copy, modify, publish, transmit, display, sell, distribute or reproduce copyrighted material, trademarks or other protected proprietary information without the express written consent of the owner of such materials.

By posting information or content to any public area of the Service, you automatically grant, and you represent and warrant that you have the right to grant the Owner and other Members an irrevocable, perpetual, non-exclusive, fully-paid, worldwide license to use, copy, perform, display and distribute such information and content and to prepare derivative works of, or incorporate into other works, such information and content, and to grant and authorize sub-licenses of the foregoing.

Your use of the service is strictly at your own risk and you are soley, whether it be written, verbal or in person, with any other Member of the Service. The Owner and its officers, directors, employees, agents, affiliates and third parties assume no responsibility whatsoever for harm that may come to you as a result of your contact (of any form) with any other Member of the Service (including but not limited to emotional, verbal and physical abuse or assault).

You will not communicate, publish or display to any other Member any form of defamatory, slanderous, offensive, inaccurate, abusive, profane, obscene, sexually offensive, threatening, harassing, racial, or illegal material, including but not limited to nude photos of yourself or others, pornographic photos or images and any other type of unlawful or unacceptable material, as decided by the Owner. The Owner reserves the right to remove any such material from the Service without notice.

You will not use the Site, Services or your profile for any purpose other than to seek other persons for meeting, friendship or dating; the Service and profiles shall not be used for any commercial purpose whatsoever (including but not limited to escorts, commercial or non-dating solicitations, or otherwise).

You will not include any contact information or identifying content of yourself or another person in your profile. In the event that such unauthorized information has been included in your profile (determined by the Site, in its sole discretion) you authorize and agree that the Site may carry out the following: (i) immediately suspend or remove your profile, until such time as the breach is remedied; or (ii) remove or obliterate all or any portion of such prohibited information, and allow the remainder of your profile to be posted on the Site.

Please note you may be involuntarily exposed to offensive or obscene materials on the Service that may have been posted by Members, hackers or unauthorized users from time to time. Please note that it is possible for others to obtain your personal information and use it to engage in an action that may be harmful to you or injure you. The Owner is not responsible for the use of any personal information that you choose to display, publish or distribute to other Members.

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. We also dislike spam as much as you do.

To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the this website. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name   
Address   
Email address  
Photo and Videos  
Personal likes/dislikes  
Email messages

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our website. THIS COOKIE DOES NOT IN ANYWAY IDENTIFY YOU OR GIVE ACCESS TO YOUR COMPUTER, and any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page (see below), and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin (see below).

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself for running this web site. We do not share this information with outside parties - except when necessary to comply with legal laws and trusted thrid-parties to run, own or administer this web site.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive, send out newsletters and other web site communications.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

If we decide to make changes to our privacy policy, we will make changes to this page.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by the Owner of this web site. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.  To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), and if you want to you can  
[opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/) or  [permanently using a browser plugin](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/intl/en/plugin/).  

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us at the CONTACT US link below.
